[Music]
hello everyone
i just wanted to give you a little bit
of an update because
i'm going to be leaving home for a
little bit
the air quality over here has been
really bad
and there's so much haze and just smog
in the air
and it's been pretty hard to tolerate
i'm usually
fairly tolerant i've been here a few
summers either visiting or living here
and we've had smoke before and i've
gotten through it pretty well but
this summer it's been different because
it's been so close to home
and so i decided that with my boyfriend
and i we would go to
the west coast for a little bit and to
distract ourselves a little bit from
everything going on over here
and get some fresh air which we both
really need
he's a surveyor and he works outdoors so
he's had to wear a really big mask
for most of it and i can't imagine it's
comfortable
so i think we're both really going to
enjoy having a bit of a break and
getting the crisp sea air which i'm very
excited for
of course i wanted to give a little more
of an
update in this video since obviously
it's
it's a little bit different it's really
hard to film out here with all the
smoke so i did want to
tell you guys a couple shenanigans i've
been up to
recently and that is
i have been raising caterpillars
being able to raise caterpillars um has
been
a possibly one of the weirdest things
i've done
so far living here i will explain i will
tell the story from the beginning
my parents had guests over at their
house
and that night the porch light
was left on and so that morning
i went over there to visit because it
was during the heatwave and i was coming
over a lot to
enjoy the ac and so i noticed
that a what i believe is a one-eyed
sphinx moth was uh at the door
and was right under the lamp and looked
very exhausted she had been
very distracted by the light that had
been left on
and she had also been heavily pregnant
and so she had left all these little
eggs
on a windowsill nearby i felt really bad
because
moss like that should leave their eggs
on
trees for example the sphinx moths eat
willow leaves and so she if she hadn't
been distracted by the light she would
have probably
flown to a nearby willow tree and had
her babies there
the eggs from the moth have a residue on
them
that makes them stick to anything they
come in contact with and so it would be
really tricky to remove them from the
windowsill
and move them to a willow tree without
breaking most of the eggs
so what i did was i put fresh willow
leaves around the eggs waiting for them
to be born
and then i had about 60 caterpillars
after about a week or two and they were
all climbing all over the windowsill and
i didn't know what to do with them
so i ended up just putting them in a
big jar with a bunch of willow leaves so
they could eat
the leaves while the other
caterpillars were being born one percent
of baby caterpillars actually make it to
adulthood
and that's because the majority of them
feed birds
and feed other creatures and it's a very
important part
of nature's life cycle and so
i went and i put a bunch in the trees
and i just kept two
because i thought it would be really
great to
take some photographs of the
caterpillars and show the whole process
of the caterpillars transforming into
moths to my former students
because they're really interested in
that whole life process and
they're always so curious and none of
them as far as i know have had the
opportunity to witness
caterpillars transform and so i wanted
to do that as well
anyway i hope to share with you an
update on the caterpillar situation
and also i will be sharing with you
next week some highlights hopefully from
my little trip
and i appreciate you watching this all
the way through if you've lasted this
long
because i clearly didn't have a plan for
this video but i still wanted to share
at least something with you
last but not least i wanted to follow
the rest of this video with a little
clip
of one of the songs that my brother
recently composed he's
a very talented musician he
recently made a lullaby that
i've been listening to and it has
brought me so much comfort
during this strange strange time in the
valley
and i i really wanted to share this
because i just thought it was beautiful
so i hope you enjoy it
and if you want to get updates on him
you can of course
follow him on instagram and get in
contact with him but
anyway i hope you have a wonderful day
and you enjoy the music
[Music]
goodbye
it's
[Music]
if we lose
we won't be too far
[Music]
apart
i don't just care
[Music]
tell them i swear
to find all that i
can give turning clowns across the skies
to give you
[Music]
it's my love's lullaby
you